Lesson 19, Nicole's close election.
Nicole loses the election at school.
She doesn't want to accept it so she looks for excuses.
Ted encourages her to accept defeat and move on.
I lost the election by a hair, just ten votes, but I'm not giving up.
Give me a break, Nicole.
You lost.
Live with it.
But I was a sure thing.
If I hadn't stayed up so late baking cookies, I wouldn't have messed up my speech.
Get real, Nicole.
It's your fault, Ted.
I lost because your friends didn't vote for me.
Don't try to put the blame on me.
I gave it my best shot.
They must have made a mistake while counting the votes.
I'll demand a recount on Monday and set the record straight.
Don't make a fool of yourself, Nicole.
Face it.
Andrea won the election fair and square.
Well, I just don't know where I went wrong.
Here, take a chocolate chip cookie.
That'll cheer you up for sure.